<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mountain Motorcycle Association of AZ</title>
    <link>http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mountain Motorcycle Association of AZ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 08:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Come Ride With Us!</title>
      <link>http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/post/come-ride-with-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 08:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/post/come-ride-with-us/</guid>
      <description>The Mountain Motorcycle Association of Arizona (MMAA) was established in 2007 and is a non-profit 501(c)(4) organization. We are dedicated to being an independent advocate for the advancement of motorcycling and the lifestyle associated with it. We actively get involved with issues that affect motorcyclists’ rights, especially in Arizona, and also promote motorcycle safety. However, our main objective (simply put) is to get out and ride! To do that, we organize and participate in many activities throughout the year that encourages our members to get out on their bikes and enjoy the beautiful area in which we live.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Charitable Events</title>
      <link>http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/post/charitable-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 07:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/post/charitable-events/</guid>
      <description>We are fortunate to call the beautiful White Mountains of Arizona our home, and we want to contribute back to the communities in which we belong. To do that, we host and participate in various events throughout the calendar year.
In the summer we host the Family Advocacy Run that helps to support the center located in Show Low, AZ. Other events help support various local Veterans organizations and raise funds for our annual Toy Drive that provide Christmas toys to needy kids in Show Low, Vernon, Heber-Overgaard, and other White Mountain areas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Activities!</title>
      <link>http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/post/fun-activities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/post/fun-activities/</guid>
      <description>Throughout the year, the MMAA hosts and participates in lots of activities. Charity events, group poker runs, highway cleanup, motorcycle safety training, camaraderie breakfasts, etc. Our members also help each other out with motorcycle maintenance and repair. There is always something fun to do!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorcycle Safety and Education</title>
      <link>http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/post/motorcycle-safety/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 07:50:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/post/motorcycle-safety/</guid>
      <description>An important part of being a MMAA member is to learn and practice new methods and techniques for improving motorcycle safety. Improve slow speed turning, counter steering, learn proper group formation riding, hand signals, braking techniques, etc. Some of our members have decades of riding experience and willingly share their knowledge to help make you a better rider!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motorcycle Rights</title>
      <link>http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/post/motorcycle-rights/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 07:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/post/motorcycle-rights/</guid>
      <description>The Mountain Motorcycle Association of Arizona is an active member of both the AZ Confederation of Motorcycle Clubs (ACMC) and ABATE of AZ. We support their efforts to lobby and educate the government and general public about motorcyclist rights, fight against discriminatory legislation, and preserve the American tradition of freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/post/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 07:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.mountainmotorcycleassociation.com/post/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>Get in touch with one of our members and come meet the rest of the group at one of our monthly meetings or camaraderie events. We look forward to meeting you!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>